

jillfetherston@gmail.com 7742281296 LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/jillianfethersto

## Frontend Software Engineer

Mainly a frontend engineer with full stack potential, I've worked with several companies across the tech spectrum since 2015. I've worked for small marketing agencies handing larger clients, I strove to bring the phrase 'wedding tech' to the mainstream, and improved KPIs within e-commerce. I'm passionate, driven, approachable, and collaborative.

# **Professional Experience**

#### Software Engineer III

Boxed | April 2019 - March 2023

- Worked as a backend engineer helping to write Boxed's SAAS catalog ingestion software
- Helped develop Boxed's SAAS front end beta application Spresso and was solely responsible for the creation of their Catalog and Bin Packing features
- Created many useful applications and features for Boxed's internal employees on their internal tools platform team
- Took ownership of Boxed's internal ads platform BAP becoming a point of knowledge for that platform

#### Frontend Engineer I Zola |

June 2017 - April 2019

- Created hundreds of wedding website themes utilizing React and Less
- Brought new features such as a revamped guest RSVP experience to Zola users
- Worked collaboratively with Registry team to bring "unification" to Zola's web
- Oversaw and mentored wedding theme creation by front end contractors

## Jr Frontend Engineer / Intern

Flightpath | September 2015 -

April 2017

- Wrote HTML emails for Time Warner Cable's marketing platform
- Worked on minor site updates for large clients such as Goya
- Played a minor but important role on Flightpath's website redesign utilizing Umbraco as the
- Helped to QA test redesign for major colostomy health organization website redesign
- Wrote Wordpress theme for Weizmann Institute blog

### Education

### Certificate in Web

**Development Immersive** 

General Assembly at Flatiron, NY | May 2015 - August 2015

GA offered a 12 week bootcamp class which I completed. We focused mostly on front end technologies - Javascript, HTML, CSS, and Angular as well as some backend technologies - Mongo DB and Postgres. I used GA as a springboard to launch

myself into a career change from food to tech and GA remains an incredibly positive formative experience.

# Bachelors in Pastry arts and hotel restaurant management

Culinary Institute of America at Hyde Park, NY| September 2006 - February 2010

Trained under top french chefs learning classical french pastry arts and hotel restaurant management. Prior to my career change, I managed a french bread bakery in Hoboken NJ for several years.

## **Key Skills**

- Javascript
- React
- Typescript
- Mongo DB
- Postgres
- Graphql
- SCSS / CSS